[{"question": "What is the Priority among (*, /, %), (+, -) and (=) C Operators.?", "option1": "A) (*, /, %) >\u00a0\u00a0(+, -) <\u00a0(=)", "option2": "B) (*, /, %) <\u00a0 (+, -) <\u00a0(=)", "option3": "C) (*, /, %) >\u00a0 (+, -) >\u00a0(=)", "option4": "D) (*, /, %) <\u00a0 (+, -)\n(+, -) ==\u00a0(=)", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C statement.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = 4 + 4/2*5 + 20;\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 40", "option2": "B) 4", "option3": "C) 34", "option4": "D) 54", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = 10 + 5 * 2 * 8 / 2 + 4;\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 124", "option2": "B) 54", "option3": "C) 23", "option4": "D) 404", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = 4 + 5/2*10 + 5;\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 29", "option2": "B) 5", "option3": "C) 4", "option4": "D) 34", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = 10 + 2 * 12 /(3*2) + 5;\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n\n", "option1": "A) 31", "option2": "B) 19", "option3": "C) 11", "option4": "D) 29", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = 10 + 2 * 12 / 3 * 2 + 5;\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 19", "option2": "B) 31", "option3": "C) 11", "option4": "D) 25", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    float a=10.0;\n    a = a % 3;\n    printf(\"%f\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 0", "option2": "B) 1", "option3": "C) 1.000000", "option4": "D) Compiler error.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    float a=10.0;\n    a = (int)a % 3;\n    printf(\"%f\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 0", "option2": "B) 1", "option3": "C) 1.000000", "option4": "D) Compiler Error.", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = 14%-5 - 2;\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 0", "option2": "B) -4", "option3": "C) -2", "option4": "D) 2", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a= 3 + 5/2;\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 3", "option2": "B) 2", "option3": "C) 5", "option4": "D) Can not assign an expression to variable at the time of declaration.", "ans": "C"}]
